Register of the Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary Sound Recordings, 1967-1980
Hoover Institution Archives
- Program list of Viewpoint and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary, 1975-1979
  - Salt II Part I, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Salt II Part II, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous III, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - New England Energy Barriers, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Land Use: The California Precedent, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Real Impact of Inflation, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Real Estate Signs, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Jonestown, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - David and Goliath, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Schools, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Budget, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Food Stamps, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Bilingual Education I, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Bilingual Education II, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Regulations Go to College, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Salcido Family, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Free Enterprise, Program 79-06, 16 April 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - T.K.E., Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Three Mile Island I, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Three Mile Island II, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Whistle Blowers; Poverty's Causes, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Parable of the Talents Updated, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
    Guest: Williams Gavin
  - McCarthy, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Grove City College, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - I'm Only 17, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Oil, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Fluid Flame Burner, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Disaster Area, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Sex Education, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Graffiti, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Banned Words, Program 79-07, 8 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - California Gas Shortage, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Oil, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Sex Education, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - People's Park I, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - People's Park II, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Free Trade vs Protectionism, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Political Bestiary, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Marijuana, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Delaney Amendment, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous I, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous II, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Investment Lag, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Crime, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Vietnam War, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Operation Get Smart, Program 79-08, 29 May 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - John Wayne, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Double Standard, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Pope in Poland, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Nuclear Power, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Oil Profits, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Money, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - A Green Lawn, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Bukovsky, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Molecules, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - A Tale of Two Countries, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Joan Baez I, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Joan Baez II, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Family, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Corruption, Program 79-09, 29 June 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Busing Amendment, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Sen. Jackson on SALT II, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Soviet Trade, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Trains, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Nigeria, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Assembly Line Medicine I, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Assembly Line Medicine II, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Namibia I, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Namibia II, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The MSHA Test, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Free Speech for Business?, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Energy-Saving Computer, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Project Match, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Elementary Energy Lessons, Program 79-10, 9 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Congressional Promises and Performance, Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Income Tax Indexation, Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Chile, Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - International Year of the Child, Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Tax Expenditures, Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Another Side of the U.N., Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - A Different Watergate Story, Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous I, Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Neoconservatives, Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Common Sense from a Neighbor, Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - America, Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous II, Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Free Speech, Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Showcase U.S.A., Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous III, Program 79-11, 27 July 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - What to Expect from the Soviet Succession, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Thank You, Chairman Brezhnev, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Better Representation for Skilled Tradesmen, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Government Housing Programs, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Alaskan Anger, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Waiting in Line, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Citizen vs Chicago Transit Authority, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Tax Revolt Going Strong, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Magic Money Machine, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Administration Report Clears, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Oil Companies, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Marijuana, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Voting Records, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Power, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Food Stamps, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Living Dangerously Sometimes, Program 79-12, 1 August 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Defense I, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Defense II, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Defense III, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Defense IV, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Talking Back, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous I, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Ships, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Salt II, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous II, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous III, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous IV, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - In Business, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - How to Handle Dissident Bureaucrats, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Local Energy Solutions, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Temperature Restrictions, Program 79-13, 11 September 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Vlasenko, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - Six Lies on Energy, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - Department of Education, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - Salt II, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - Hollywood East, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - Defectors, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - In Defense of Success, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - Coal, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - California, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - The Draft, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
    Guest: Martin Anderson
  - Red Tape, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - Radioactivity, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - The Golden Fleece, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - Gadgets, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - Land, Program 79-14, 2 October 1979 (Box 8)
  - Cuba Overseas, Program 79-15, 25 October 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Cuban Conditions, Program 79-15, 25 October 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Israel I, Program 79-15, 25 October 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Israel II, Program 79-15, 25 October 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Salt, Program 79-15, 25 October 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Health Care, Program 79-15, 25 October 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous and Goodbye, Program 79-15, 25 October 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)